Guide to Records of the Office of the President (John Brademas) RG.3.0.10
New York University Archives
- Series XI. Schools and Divisions, 1977-1991; 20.43 Linear Feet in 49 manuscript boxes.
  - School of Education, Health, Nursing, and Arts Professions RESTRICTED, 1989, 1991 (Box 198, Folder 1-3)
  - Center for Educational Technology and Economic Productivity, 1989 (Box 199, Folder 3)
  - Institute of Fine Arts -- Board of Trustees RESTRICTED, 1989-1991 (Box 198, Folder 1-8, Box 200, Folder 1)
  - School of Law and Financial Aid Study RESTRICTED, 1991 (Box 200, Folder 2)
  - School of Law RESTRICTED, 1990 (Box 200, Folder 3)
  - School of Law -- Law Center Foundation RESTRICTED, 1989 (Box 200, Folder 4)
  - School of Law -- Law Center Foundation Board of Trustees RESTRICTED, 1990-1991 (Box 200, Folder 5-7)
  - School of Law -- Financial Aid Study, 1990 (Box 199, Folder 4-5)
  - Medical Center RESTRICTED, 1991 (Box 200, Folder 8)
  - Medical Center RESTRICTED, 1990 (Box 200, Folder 9-11)
  - Medical Center -- Tisch Hospital RESTRICTED, 1989 (Box 201, Folder 1-4)
  - Medical Center Board of Trustees RESTRICTED, 1991 (Box 201, Folder 5)
  - Medical Center, 1989 (Box 199, Folder 6)
  - Medical Center -- Finance Committee RESTRICTED, 1990 (Box 201, Folder 6)
  - Medical Center RESTRICTED, 1989 (Box 201, Folder 7)
  - Medical Center Board of Trustees RESTRICTED, 1989-1991 (Box 201, Folder 8, Box 202, Folder 1-6, Box 203, Folder 1-5)
  - Medical Center Board Member Lists RESTRICTED, 1988-1990 (Box 203, Folder 6-7)
  - Medical Center RESTRICTED, 1989 (Box 203, Folder 8)
  - Medical Center Joint Trust Committee RESTRICTED, 1991 (Box 203, Folder 9)
  - Medical Center Board RESTRICTED, 1989 (Box 203, Folder 10)
  - Medical Center -- Rusk Institute of Rehabilitation Medicine RESTRICTED, 1989-1990 (Box 203, Folder 11, Box 204, Folder 1)
  - Robert F. Wagner Graduate School of Public Service RESTRICTED, 1989-1991 (Box 204, Folder 2-4)
  - Correspondence re: Higher Education Conference, 1990 (Box 199, Folder 7)
  - Robert F. Wagner Graduate School of Public Service -- Urban Research Center, 1989-1990 (Box 199, Folder 8-9)
  - School of Social Services RESTRICTED, 1990 (Box 204, Folder 5)
  - College of Arts and Science, 1988 (Box 199, Folder 10)
  - Deutsches Haus Advisory Board, 1990 (Box 199, Folder 11)
  - Deutsches Haus, 1989 (Box 199, Folder 12)
  - College of Arts and Science Faculty Meeting, 1990-1991 (Box 199, Folder 13-14)
  - College of Arts and Science Board of Overseers Member List, 1989 (Box 199, Folder 15)
  - Institute for the Humanities, 1989 (Box 199, Folder 16)
  - Society of Fellows RESTRICTED, 1991 (Box 204, Folder 6)
  - Hagop Kevorkian Center for Near Eastern Studies, 1990 (Box 199, Folder 17)
  - Hagop Kevorkian Center for Near Eastern Studies RESTRICTED, 1989 (Box 204, Folder 7)
  - Department of Applied Science, 1989 (Box 199, Folder 18)
  - French Programs, 1989 (Box 199, Folder 19)
  - NYU in Spain, 1989 (Box 199, Folder 20)
  - Graduate School of Arts and Science -- Museum Studies Program, 1990 (Box 199, Folder 21)
  - Center for War, Peace, and the News Media RESTRICTED, 1991 (Box 204, Folder 8)
  - Center for War, Peace, and the News Media -- Gulf War Media Project, 1991 (Box 205, Folder 1)
  - Center for French Civilization, 1989 (Box 205, Folder 2)
  - Asian Studies, 1990-1991 (Box 205, Folder 3)
  - Center for War, Peace, and the News Media -- Europe's New Architecture, 1990 (Box 205, Folder 4-6)
  - Center for War, Peace, and the News Media -- U.S. and Soviet Issues, 1989 (Box 205, Folder 7-8, Box 206, Folder 1)
  - American Rhodes Scholarship Trust, 1990 (Box 206, Folder 2)
  - Gallatin Division -- Graduate Program in Publishing Studies RESTRICTED, 1991 (Box 204, Folder 9)
  - Gallatin Division -- Creative Arts Team, 1990 (Box 206, Folder 3-4)
  - Gallatin Division RESTRICTED, 1989-1990 (Box 204, Folder 10)
  - Tisch School of the Arts RESTRICTED, 1984-1986 (Box 204, Folder 11-12)
  - Correspondence, 1985 (Box 206, Folder 4)
  - Graduate School of Public Administration, 1986 (Box 206, Folder 6)
  - Graduate School of Arts and Science RESTRICTED, 1984-1986 (Box 204, Folder 13)
  - College of Arts and Science RESTRICTED, 1983-1986 (Box 207, Folder 1)
  - Dental Center, 1983-1984 (Box 206, Folder 7)
  - Medical Center Board Meeting RESTRICTED, 1984, 1986 (Box 207, Folder 2)
  - Medical Center Board Executive Committee Meeting RESTRICTED, 1984 (Box 207, Folder 3)
  - Medical Center -- Ambulatory Care Study Report, 1986 (Box 206, Folder 8-9)
  - The Urban Research Center -- Report and Proposal to the Charles H. Revson Foundation, 1985 (Box 208, Folder 1)
  - Medical Center -- Strategic Plan for the 1990s, 1986 (Box 208, Folder 2)
  - Medical Center, 1984-1986 (Box 208, Folder 3-4)
  - Medical Center RESTRICTED, 1984-1986 (Box 207, Folder 4)
  - Medical Center Operating Budget for FY 1985-1986 (Box 208, Folder 5)
  - Medical Center Financial Statements, 1983, 1985-1986 (Box 208, Folder 6-7)
  - Medical Center Reports, 1985 (Box 209, Folder 1)
  - Medical Center Board of Trustees RESTRICTED, 1985 (Box 207, Folder 5)
  - Courant Institute of Mathematical Sciences -- Proposed Center for Advanced Scientific Computing, 1984 (Box 209, Folder 2)
  - Courant Institute of Mathematical Sciences -- Department of Energy RESTRICTED, 1984 (Box 207, Folder 6)
  - The Urban Research Center of New York University: Report and Proposal to the Charles H. Revson Foundation, 1986 (Box 209, Folder 3)
  - Tisch School of the Arts RESTRICTED, 1987 (Box 207, Folder 7)
  - College of Business and Public Administration RESTRICTED, 1987 (Box 207, Folder 8)
  - Graduate School of Business Administration RESTRICTED, 1987 (Box 207, Folder 9)
  - Graduate School of Business Administration -- U.S.-Japan Center, 1986-1987 (Box 209, Folder 4)
  - College of Arts and Science RESTRICTED, 1987 (Box 207, Folder 10)
  - School of Continuing Education RESTRICTED, 1985, 1987 (Box 207, Folder 11)
  - Courant Institute of Mathematical Sciences, 1987 (Box 209, Folder 5)
  - Selim and Rachel Benin Scholarship Fund, 1987 (Box 209, Folder 6)
  - Dental Clinic Fact Sheet, 1987 (Box 209, Folder 7)
  - School of Education, Health, Nursing, and Arts Professions -- Metropolitan Center for Educational Research RESTRICTED, 1987 (Box 207, Folder 12)
  - General Correspondence, 1987 (Box 209, Folder 8)
  - Institute of Fine Arts -- Funding RESTRICTED, 1987 (Box 210, Folder 1)
  - Institute of Fine Arts Board of Trustees RESTRICTED, 1984-1987 (Box 210, Folder 2-4)
  - College of Arts and Science -- Skirball Department of Hebrew and Judaic Studies, 1987 (Box 209, Folder 9)
  - State Government -- Dental Center, 1983-1985 (Box 209, Folder 10)
  - College of Arts and Science -- Dean Search RESTRICTED, 1985 (Box 210, Folder 5)
  - Federal Affairs -- Medical Center RESTRICTED, 1985 (Box 210, Folder 6)
  - Construction Projects RESTRICTED, 1984-1985 (Box 210, Folder 7)
  - Courant Institute of Mathematical Sciences, 1985 (Box 209, Folder 11)
  - Graduate School of Business Administration -- Dean Search RESTRICTED, 1985 (Box 210, Folder 8)
  - School of Education, Health, Nursing, and Arts Professions -- Rosovsky Report on Hebrew and Judaic Studies Department -- R.B. Winder RESTRICTED, 1985 (Box 210, Folder 9)
  - Group from People's Republic of China Visit NYU Computer Facilities, 1985 (Box 209, Folder 12)
  - Medical Center Issues RESTRICTED, 1984-1985 (Box 210, Folder 10)
  - Neural Science Center, 1987 (Box 141, Folder 1)
  - College of Arts and Science -- Italian Program, 1987 (Box 141, Folder 2)
  - Center for War, Peace, and the News Media -- Annual Report, 1987 (Box 141, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1987-1988 (Box 141, Folder 4)
  - Onassis Center for Hellenic Studies -- Director Search (A-J) RESTRICTED, 1987 (Box 230, Folder 1-2)
  - Onassis Center for Hellenic Studies -- Director Search (K-Z) RESTRICTED, 1987 (Box 230, Folder 3-4)
  - Onassis Center for Hellenic Studies (A-G) Agreements, Convocation RESTRICTED, 1986 (Box 230, Folder 5, Box 231, Folder 1)
  - Onassis Center for Hellenic Studies (H-N) RESTRICTED, 1986 (Box 231, Folder 2-3)
  - Onassis Center for Hellenic Studies (O-Z) RESTRICTED, 1986 (Box 231, Folder 4-5)
  - Onassis Center for Hellenic Studies RESTRICTED, 1981-1982 (Box 232, Folder 1)
  - Onassis Center for Hellenic Studies RESTRICTED, 1983-1985 (Box 231, Folder 6-7)
  - Law School -- Construction, 1987 (Box 141, Folder 5)
  - Law School -- Construction RESTRICTED, 1987 (Box 232, Folder 2-3)
  - Law Center Foundation -- Board of Trustees RESTRICTED, 1987 (Box 232, Folder 4)
  - Medical Center -- Fundraising RESTRICTED, 1987 (Box 232, Folder 5)
  - Medical Center -- Clinical Research Center RESTRICTED, 1987 (Box 232, Folder 6)
  - Medical Center, 1987 (Box 141, Folder 6-7)
  - Medical Center -- Board of Trustees RESTRICTED, 1987 (Box 232, Folder 7-8)
  - Medical Center -- Board of Trustees RESTRICTED, 1987 (Box 233, Folder 1-3)
  - Medical Center -- Staff RESTRICTED, 1987 (Box 233, Folder 4)
  - Graduate School of Public Administration RESTRICTED, 1987 (Box 233, Folder 5)
  - Urban Research Center RESTRICTED, 1987 (Box 233, Folder 6)
  - College of Arts and Science -- Board of Overseers RESTRICTED, 1987 (Box 233, Folder 7-8)
  - School of Social Work, 1987 (Box 141, Folder 8)
  - C.V. Starr Center for Applied Economics RESTRICTED, 1987 (Box 233, Folder 9)
  - Society of Fellows, 1987 (Box 141, Folder 9)
  - President's Council on Near East Studies, 1987 (Box 141, Folder 10)
  - Department of French and Italian -- Annual Report, 1987 (Box 141, Folder 11)
  - Medical Center -- Financing RESTRICTED, 1984-1986 (Box 234, Folder 1)
  - Medical Center -- Financing, 1984-1986 (Box 142, Folder 1-2)
  - Medical Center -- Board of Trustees RESTRICTED, 1984-1986 (Box 234, Folder 2-6)
  - Medical Center, 1984-1986 (Box 142, Folder 3)
  - Medical Center RESTRICTED, 1985-1986 (Box 234, Folder 7)
  - Rusk Institute of Rehabilitation Medicine RESTRICTED, 1983-1986 (Box 234, Folder 8)
  - Medical Center -- Bellevue RESTRICTED, 1985 (Box 234, Folder 9)
  - Medical Center -- Bellevue Hospital Association, 1984 (Box 142, Folder 4)
  - Medical Center -- Kaplan Cancer Center, 1985 (Box 142, Folder 5)
  - Graduate School of Business Administration RESTRICTED, 1984-1985 (Box 235, Folder 1)
  - Urban Research Center RESTRICTED, 1984-1986 (Box 235, Folder 2-3)
  - Naming Opportunities for New and Renovated Facilities -- Committee for the Year 2000 RESTRICTED, 1986 (Box 235, Folder 4)
  - School of Social Work RESTRICTED, 1985-1986 (Box 235, Folder 5)
  - Housing RESTRICTED, 1984-1986 (Box 235, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence RESTRICTED, 1984-1986 (Box 235, Folder 7)
  - College of Arts and Science RESTRICTED, 1984-1986 (Box 235, Folder 8)
  - Institute of Fine Arts RESTRICTED, 1985-1986 (Box 235, Folder 9)
  - Center for Japan -- U.S. Business and Economic Studies, 1984-1986 (Box 142, Folder 6)
  - New York Institute for the Humanities, 1984 (Box 142, Folder 7)
  - Kevorkian Center for Near East Studies, 1984-1986 (Box 142, Folder 8)
  - Study Abroad Programs, 1985 (Box 142, Folder 9)
  - Faculty of Arts and Science Meetings RESTRICTED, 1984-1986 (Box 235, Folder 10)
  - Château de Beynac RESTRICTED, 1985 (Box 235, Folder 11)
  - Institute of French Studies, 1983-1986 (Box 142, Folder 10)
  - New York University in Spain, 1984-1986 (Box 142, Folder 11)
  - Center for War, Peace, and the News Media, 1984-1986 (Box 142, Folder 12-13)
  - Casa Hispanica, 1984 (Box 226, Folder 1)
  - Urban Research Center, 1984-1986 (Box 226, Folder 2)
  - Gallatin Division RESTRICTED, 1984-1986 (Box 236, Folder 1)
  - Real Estate Institute Advisory Board RESTRICTED, 1985-1986 (Box 236, Folder 2)
  - Courant Institute of Mathematical Sciences, 1984-1986 (Box 226, Folder 3-4)
  - College of Dentistry RESTRICTED, 1984-1986 (Box 236, Folder 3-4)
  - College of Dentistry, 1984-1986 (Box 226, Folder 5)
  - Medical Center, 1984 (Box 226, Folder 6)
  - Medical Center Board, 1984 (Box 226, Folder 7)
  - College of Dentistry -- Funding, 1984-1986 (Box 226, Folder 8)
  - SEHNAP RESTRICTED, 1984-1986 (Box 236, Folder 5-6)
  - SEHNAP, 1985-1986 (Box 226, Folder 9)
  - Medical Center Development Meeting RESTRICTED, 1984 (Box 236, Folder 7)
  - School of Law, 1984-1985 (Box 226, Folder 10)
  - School of Law RESTRICTED, 1984-1986 (Box 237, Folder 1)
  - Law Center Foundation -- Board of Trustees RESTRICTED, 1984-1986 (Box 237, Folder 2-4)
  - Medical Center RESTRICTED, 1984-1986 (Box 237, Folder 5)
  - Medical Center Board, 1984-1986 (Box 226, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, 1984, 1986 (Box 226, Folder 12)
  - Le Chateau de Menars RESTRICTED, 1984-1986 (Box 237, Folder 6-7)
  - College of Arts and Science RESTRICTED, 1986 (Box 237, Folder 8)
  - Urban Research Center, 1984 (Box 227, Folder 1)
  - Graduate School of Business Administration RESTRICTED, 1984-1986 (Box 237, Folder 9, Box 238, Folder 1)
  - Graduate School of Business Administration RESTRICTED, 1983-1986 (Box 238, Folder 2-3)
  - Institute of Retail Management, 1985 (Box 227, Folder 2)
  - College of Business and Public Administration RESTRICTED, 1984-1986 (Box 238, Folder 4)
  - School of Continuing Education, 1985-1986 (Box 227, Folder 3)
  - School of Continuing Education RESTRICTED, 1984-1986 (Box 238, Folder 5-7)
  - Endowed and Unendowed Professorships for NYU, 1985 (Box 227, Folder 4-5)
  - College of Arts and Science -- Proposed 1987-1988 Staffing Plan, 1986 (Box 227, Folder 6)
  - Graduate School of Arts and Science Planning Report 1987-1988, 1986 (Box 227, Folder 7)
  - Planning Reports from Various NYU School and Divisions, 1985-1987 (Box 227, Folder 8-9)
  - Division of Libraries Five Year Plan 1987-1992, 1986 (Box 228, Folder 1)
  - Five Year Plans for Various NYU Schools and Divisions, 1986-1987 (Box 228, Folder 2-4)
  - Analysis of Federal FY1988 Budget Proposals and Impact on NYU, circa 1986-1986 (Box 228, Folder 5-6)
  - Greek Culture Center, 1981-1982 (Box 229, Folder 1)
  - La Pietra Clipping, 1983 (Box 229, Folder 2)
  - Executive Management Training in Athens Program (NYU / EMTA) -- Background, 1982-1983 (Box 229, Folder 3-4)
  - Executive Management Training in Athens Program (NYU / EMTA) -- Greek Trip Background Correspondence, 1982-1983 (Box 229, Folder 5-6)
  - Executive Management Training in Athens Program (NYU / EMTA) -- Preliminary Material, 1982 (Box 229, Folder 7)
  - Executive Management Training in Athens Program (NYU / EMTA) -- Proposal, January 1983 Version (Box 229, Folder 8)
  - Executive Management Training in Athens Program (NYU / EMTA) -- Briefing Book, Greece, 1983-01-08-1983-01-10 (Box 180, Folder 1)
  - Executive Management Training in Athens Program (NYU / EMTA) Program -- Daily Briefing Book, Greece, 1983-01-08-1983-01-10 (Box 180, Folder 2-3)
  - Executive Management Training in Athens Program (NYU / EMTA) -- Greek Trip, 1983-01-08-1983-01-10 (Box 180, Folder 4-5)
  - Greek Cultural Center -- Proposed Informational Materials, circa 1982-1983 (Box 180, Folder 6)
  - Executive Management Training in Athens Program -- Greek Trip Follow-up, January 1983 (Box 180, Folder 7)
  - Executive Management Training in Athens Program (NYU / EMTA) -- Planning Meeting, 1983-01-13 (Box 180, Folder 8)
  - Executive Management Training in Athens Program (NYU / EMTA) -- Greece Trip, January 1983 (Box 180, Folder 9)
  - Executive Management Training in Athens Program (NYU / EMTA) -- Greek-American Press Briefing, 1983-02-09 (Box 181, Folder 1)
  - Executive Management Training in Athens Program (NYU / EMTA) -- Greek Trip Follow-Up, 1983 (Box 181, Folder 2)
  - Executive Management Training in Athens Program (NYU / EMTA) -- Thank You Letters re: Greece Trip, February 1983 (Box 181, Folder 3)
  - Executive Management Training in Athens Program (NYU / EMTA) -- Coordination Correspondence RESTRICTED, February -- March 1983 (Box 140, Folder 3-4)
  - Executive Management Training in Athens Program (NYU / EMTA) -- Briefing Book and Working Book, June 1983 (Box 181, Folder 4-5)
  - Executive Management Training in Athens Program (NYU / EMTA), 1983 (Box 181, Folder 6)
  - Executive Management Training in Athens Program (NYU / EMTA) -- Papandreou Letter -- Original RESTRICTED, 1983 (Box 140, Folder 5)
  - Executive Management Training in Athens Program (NYU / EMTA) -- Gerassimos Arsenis -- Background RESTRICTED, 1983 (Box 140, Folder 6)
  - Executive Management Training in Athens Program (NYU / EMTA) -- Brochure and Application Form Planning, 1983 (Box 181, Folder 7)
  - Executive Management Training in Athens Program (NYU / EMTA) -- Brochure and Application Form Planning, 1983 (Box 181, Folder 8)
  - Executive Management Training in Athens Program (NYU / EMTA) -- Certificates, circa 1983 (Box 182, Folder 1)
  - NYU Bulletin, 1985-1968 -- Edited (Box 182, Folder 2)
  - Planning Commission Study Group, 1985 (Box 182, Folder 3)
  - Five Year Planning Report -- Arts and Science, February 1987 (Box 182, Folder 4)
  - Six Year Report, 1987 (Box 182, Folder 5-7)
  - Long-Range Plan -- Interim Report of the University-wide Planning Commission -- Summary Reports, October 1988 (Box 182, Folder 8-9)
  - Onassis Center for Hellenic Studies, 1989-1990 (Box 222, Folder 5)
  - Faculty Resource Network Summer Events, 1990 (Box 222, Folder 6)
  - NYU Yeronisos Island Excavation and Training Program, 1990 (Box 222, Folder 7)
  - Spanish House at NYU Concept, 1990 (Box 222, Folder 8)
- Series XII. Student Affairs, 1971-1991; 6.70 Linear Feet in 16 manuscript boxes.
  This series contains subjects relating to NYU students, including financial aid; housing; South African students at NYU; fraternities; sports teams; and student groups, such as the Gay Students Union. Files date from 1971 to 1991 and typically contain correspondence, reports, magazine articles, and press clippings. There are a significant number of files in this series containing admissions statistical reports and admission intervention request-related correspondence.
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged in chronological order.
  - Admissions RESTRICTED, 1988 (Box 194, Folder 6)
  - Financial Aid RESTRICTED, 1988 (Box 194, Folder 7, Box 196, Folder 1-3)
  - Reports, 1988 (Box 211, Folder 1)
  - Student Loan Issues RESTRICTED, 1980-1982 (Box 212, Folder 1)
  - Report of the NYU Intercollegiate Athletics Advisory Committee, 1971-1982 (Box 211, Folder 2)
  - Gay Students' Union, 1981-1982 (Box 211, Folder 3)
  - Student Housing Issues RESTRICTED, 1980-1982 (Box 212, Folder 2)
  - Student Aid RESTRICTED, 1981-1982 (Box 212, Folder 3-4)
  - Scholarships and Awards RESTRICTED, 1980-1982 (Box 212, Folder 5)
  - Publications -- Newspapers, 1981 (Box 211, Folder 4)
  - Student Groups, 1981-1982 (Box 211, Folder 5)
  - Financial Aid RESTRICTED, 1982-1984 (Box 212, Folder 6-7)
  - Financial Aid -- Loans, 1982 (Box 211, Folder 6)
  - Financial Aid -- Scholarships and Grants RESTRICTED, 1982-1983 (Box 212, Folder 8)
  - South Africa Education Program, 1980-1981 (Box 211, Folder 7)
  - Integration of Business Schools, circa 1982 (Box 211, Folder 8)
  - Placement Services, 1982 (Box 211, Folder 9)
  - Student Correspondence RESTRICTED, 1982-1985 (Box 213, Folder 1)
  - Tzong-Huey Lin RESTRICTED, 1980-1981 (Box 213, Folder 2)
  - United Negro College Fund (UNCF) Study of Black Students, 1981 (Box 211, Folder 10)
  - Application Process Issues RESTRICTED, 1981-1982 (Box 213, Folder 3)
  - Application Statistics Reports, 1981-1982 (Box 211, Folder 11-12)
  - Admissions: Interventions RESTRICTED, 1981-1983 (Box 213, Folder 4-7)
  - Graduate Student Orientation, 1984 (Box 211, Folder 13)
  - Office of the Registrar Enrollment Reports, 1983-1985 (Box 211, Folder 14-15)
  - Admissions Interventions RESTRICTED, 1984 (Box 213, Folder 8, Box 214, Folder 1)
  - Admissions Statistical Reports, 1984-1985 (Box 215, Folder 1)
  - NCAA Classification, 1984 (Box 215, Folder 2)
  - Fencing Championship, 1984 (Box 215, Folder 3)
  - Political Science Graduate Student Association, 1985 (Box 215, Folder 4)
  - FIJI (Phi Gamma Delta) Fraternity, 1985, 1987 (Box 215, Folder 5)
  - Student Senate, 1984 (Box 215, Folder 6)
  - Student Senator Council, 1985 (Box 215, Folder 7)
  - Student Health Services, 1984-1985 (Box 215, Folder 8)
  - Student Housing Issues RESTRICTED, 1984-1985 (Box 214, Folder 2)
  - Financial Aid RESTRICTED, 1984-1985 (Box 214, Folder 3-4)
  - Scholarships RESTRICTED, 1984-1985 (Box 214, Folder 5)
  - South African Education Program, 1984-1988 (Box 215, Folder 9)
  - Project Opportunity, 1984-1985 (Box 215, Folder 10)
  - Admission Intervention RESTRICTED, 1984-1985 (Box 214, Folder 6-7)
  - Condolence Letters RESTRICTED, 1985 (Box 214, Folder 8)
  - Admission Intervention RESTRICTED, 1985-1986 (Box 214, Folder 9, Box 216, Folder 1-2, Box 217)
  - Correspondence re: Student and Staff Issues RESTRICTED, 1983-1985 (Box 216, Folder 3-5)
  - Sports, 1987 (Box 215, Folder 11)
  - Students Requests for Acceptance RESTRICTED, 1986 (Box 217, Folder 3)
  - Student Deposit Statistics, 1987 (Box 215, Folder 12)
  - Reports, 1986 (Box 215, Folder 13)
  - Admission Requests RESTRICTED, 1987 (Box 217, Folder 4-5)
  - Correspondence re: Student Issues RESTRICTED, 1986-1987 (Box 218, Folder 1-5)
  - Sports and Recreation Development, 1986 (Box 215, Folder 14)
  - Gay and Lesbian Union, 1986-1987 (Box 215, Folder 15)
  - Collegiate Association for the Research of Principles (CARP) Convention, 1986 (Box 215, Folder 16)
  - Psi Upsilon Building, 1985-1986 (Box 215, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence, 1987 (Box 215, Folder 18)
  - Report of Drug Use Survey, 1986 (Box 215, Folder 19)
  - Student Residence Issues RESTRICTED, 1986, 1988 (Box 219, Folder 1)
  - Student Issues RESTRICTED, 1986-1988 (Box 219, Folder 2)
  - Internal Communications, 1987 (Box 215, Folder 20)
  - Awards and Internships, 1986 (Box 215, Folder 21)
  - School of Education, Health, Nursing, and Arts Professions Yearbook, 1987, 1989 (Box 215, Folder 22)
  - Student Publications, 1986 (Box 215, Folder 23)
  - Reports of Registration, 1986 (Box 215, Folder 24)
  - Student Issues RESTRICTED, 1984 (Box 219, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1988-1991 (Box 220, Folder 1)
  - Internal Communications, 1988, 1990 (Box 220, Folder 2)
  - FY 1988 Annual Survey of Students Charges and Financial Aid Grants (Box 220, Folder 3)
  - Executive Development Committee Meeting RESTRICTED, 1989 (Box 219, Folder 4)
  - Faculty Resource Network: Report on Activities, 1989-1990 (Box 220, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence RESTRICTED, 1988 (Box 219, Folder 5-7)
  - Correspondence RESTRICTED, 1990-1991 (Box 221, Folder 1)
  - Cambridge Associates Report on Student Charges, 1990 (Box 220, Folder 5)
  - Harvard Gazette Article, 1989 (Box 220, Folder 6)
  - Student Enrollment Reports, 1989 (Box 220, Folder 7)
  - Sports and Recreation, 1989-1990 (Box 220, Folder 8)
  - Sigma Phi Epsilon, 1989 (Box 220, Folder 9)
  - AAUS Conference, 1990 (Box 220, Folder 10)
  - Student Housing Issues RESTRICTED, 1989-1991 (Box 221, Folder 2)
  - Student Financial Aid Issues RESTRICTED, 1990 (Box 221, Folder 3)
  - Social Sciences Research Council's International Predissertation Fellowship Program Issue, 1990-1991 (Box 220, Folder 11)
  - Scholarships RESTRICTED, 1989 (Box 221, Folder 4)
  - South African Program, 1989-1990 (Box 222, Folder 1)
  - First Cross-School Schedule of Classes, Fall, 1989 (Box 222, Folder 2)
  - College of Arts and Science Year Book Presidential Letter, 1991 (Box 222, Folder 3)
  - Student Issues RESTRICTED, 1991 (Box 221, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence RESTRICTED, 1990 (Box 221, Folder 6-7)
  - Correspondence RESTRICTED, 1989-1990 (Box 223, Folder 1-4)
  - Data on Student Aid, 1982 (Box 241, Folder 3-4)
  - The Changing Demand for Educational Skills, 1982 (Box 241, Folder 5)
  - Gambling with Our Future -- Final Staff Draft, 1983 (Box 241, Folder 6)